Daniel Epstein

Front End Web Developer

Enthusiastic front end web developer with a passion for designing clean, simple, focused, and elegant code. With experience in React, Redux, Webpack, SCSS, Jest, Enzyme and a background in C++ and Java, I discovered web development through my colleagues at NYCDA.



Personal Info

Address

58-05 Metropolitan Ave

Phone

347-357-0712

E-mail

d.epstein92@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/danielepstein-9963b113a/



Skills

React

Javascript

Redux

Webpack

Jest

Enzyme

SCSS



Experience

2018-09 - Front End Developer Intern

2018-12 Company: ParkField Commerce

Experience using Shopify Liquid to create thoughtful user content.

Experience Using SCSS to create dynamic and user friendly UI.

Experience using DOM manipulation for event content.

Worked with clients directly to address client concerns.

Worked with UI/UX designers to design user content.



Education

Full Stack Developer - New York Code and Design Academy

Successfully completed 240 hours, Part-Time Web Development Intensive. Worked with technologies such as React, Redux, SCSS, Webpack, and Firebase.

2014-09 - Computer Information Systems Associate of Applied Science (AAS) Degree - BramsonOrt College

The Computer Programming concentration trains students to solve real world business problem using a structured programming approach. That approach involves using popular software languages such as C++, C#, Java, Visual Basic and .Net Programming.



Skay Beauty Palace

React, Redux, Webpack, SCSS

An online store created for Cosmetologist Rashawna Green. At Skay Beauty Palace you can shop for custom lashes, weaves, and nails! You can view, rate and purchase products in stock. Looking to make an appointment with Ms. Green? You can make an appointment to have lashes, weaves, or nails done and an email confirmation with the time, day and month will be sent to your email! (MailChimp)

Task_Turtle

React, Redux, Webpack, SCSS, Semantic-UI-React, Jest, Enzyme, Flask
A website where you can bid for jobs and get tasks! Users can request jobs,
receive messages from employers, post profile pictures, update skills and
share to social media. Made with TDD with Jest and Enzyme each
functionality is tested. BEM methodology for readability and re-usable style
sheets.